[{"question": "Neural networks are", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Linear models", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Non-linear models", "correct": true}, {"answer": "Linear regression models", "correct": false}, {"answer": "None of the above", "correct": false}], "tag": "neural_network", "lecture_file": "21_machine_learning"}, {"question": "A data set can be represented with only a unique neural network model", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "FALSE", "correct": true}, {"answer": "TRUE", "correct": false}], "tag": "neural_network", "lecture_file": "21_machine_learning"}, {"question": "Neural networks are very useful models because", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "They accurately represent biological neurons", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Theoretically, they can fit to any data set", "correct": true}, {"answer": "You don\u2019t need to train them", "correct": false}, {"answer": "They can extrapolate in an accurate manner", "correct": false}], "tag": "neural_network", "lecture_file": "21_machine_learning"}, {"question": "The nature of extrapolation from a neural network depends a lot on", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "the activation functions", "correct": true}, {"answer": "size of the data set", "correct": false}, {"answer": "number of hidden layers", "correct": false}, {"answer": "number of neurons", "correct": false}], "tag": "activation_function hyperparameters", "lecture_file": "21_machine_learning"}, {"question": "The hyperparameters for a neural network are", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "The number of neurons in a layer", "correct": false}, {"answer": "The activation function", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Number of hidden layers", "correct": false}, {"answer": "All of the above", "correct": true}], "tag": "hyperparameters", "lecture_file": "21_machine_learning"}, {"question": "Gradient descent updates the hyperparameters after each", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Epoch", "correct": true}, {"answer": "layer", "correct": false}, {"answer": "data point", "correct": false}, {"answer": "None of the above", "correct": false}], "tag": "gradient_descent algorithm", "lecture_file": "21_machine_learning"}, {"question": "For a neural network with the architecture:<br>Input layer = 3 features<br>first layer = 3 neurons<br>second layer = 5 neurons<br>output layer = 1 output variable<br>How many weights are involved between the first and second layer?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "9", "correct": false}, {"answer": "3", "correct": false}, {"answer": "15", "correct": true}, {"answer": "5", "correct": false}], "tag": "weights_biases algorithm", "lecture_file": "21_machine_learning"}, {"question": "The gradient descent algorithm leads to at least a local minimum of", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "weights and biases", "correct": false}, {"answer": "output", "correct": false}, {"answer": "The objective function", "correct": true}, {"answer": "None of the above", "correct": false}], "tag": "gradient_descent algorithm", "lecture_file": "21_machine_learning"}, {"question": "What is the value of the count of total weights and biases for a neural network which has 2 hidden layers (3 neurons in each) between the input (2 inputs) and output (1 output)?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "10", "correct": false}, {"answer": "81", "correct": false}, {"answer": "25", "correct": true}, {"answer": "18", "correct": false}], "tag": "weights_biases algorithm", "lecture_file": "21_machine_learning"}, {"question": "The statement: 'A higher learning rate will result in quickly reaching the optimum parameters of a neural network', is", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Never true", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Always true", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Can be true only for learning rates above a certain threshold", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Can be true, but can also cause the solver to not converge.", "correct": true}], "tag": "learning_rate", "lecture_file": "21_machine_learning"}]